I got a new life
You would hardly recognize me I'm so glad
How could a person like me care for you
Why do I bother
When you're not the one for me
Oooo, is enough, enough
I saw the sign and it opened up my eyes I saw the sign
Life is demanding without understanding
No one's gonna drag you up to get into the light where you belong
But where do you belong
Under the pale moon
For so many years I've wondered who you are
How can a person like you bring me joy
Under the pale moon
Where I see a lot of stars
Is enough, enough
I saw the sign and it opened up my eyes I saw the sign
Life is demanding without understanding
No one's gonna drag you up to get into the light where you belong
But where do you belong
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
I saw the sign and it opened up my mind
And I am happy now living without you
I've left you, ooohhh
I saw the sign and it opened up my eyes I saw the sign
No one's gonna drag you up to get into the light where you belong
I saw the sign - I saw the sign - I saw the sign
And it opened up my eyes I saw the sign
subbastian